

DOMEN ŠINKOVEC

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Strips d.o.o. Kandrše del 7, 1252 Vače 2018 - 2024

Programmer/operator of technological devices producing PCB circuits.

Kopit d.o.o. Šmartno pri Litiji 2016-2018

Student job working on CNC machines making metal products!

Elektro Šinkovec Slivna 2014 - 2016

Student job installing, repairing and maintaining electrical networks.

EDUCATION

ABOUT ME

I'm a self-taught frontend developer. I have been coding for over two years while working in a different field. Programming has become my

passion, and I've been dedicating my free time to learning, building

opportunity in the industry, where I could get a job where I can work

with experienced developers, gain mentorship, and contribute with my enthusiasm for web development. I believe that learning never stops,

projects, and improving my skills. I'm now looking for my first

and I'm excited to take the next step in my career as a frontend

ŠCPET, School Center for Post, Economy, and Telecommunications, Celjska ulica 16, 1000 Ljubljana

2010 - 2014

developer.

Studied telecommunications

domen.sinkovec@gmail.com

CONTACT

031-862-526

1274 Litija

- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT
- TAILWINDCSS
- SUPABASE

LANGUAGES

- English(advanced)
- German(basic)



EAT AND SPLICE

This project made with ReactJS helps you to calculate expenses between you and your friend when paying the bill in a restaurant.

TODO APP

PROJECTS

Todo App made with NextJS and Supabase backend. Users can login where they can see their tasks.

INESTYLE

This is a page I made for my good friend Ines when she opened her hair and beauty saloon. It is made with ReactJS and TailwindCSS.



SKILLS